Washington Star 061 061
Stage
- Series 5: General Operations, 1868-1981
  - Training Program, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Truck Accidents, 1970-1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Trucks, 1969-1976 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Weekly Reports, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Zayre Department Store Inserts, 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Clippings re: Evening Star, 1946-1977 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Clippings re: Evening Star, 1946-1977 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Clippings re: Evening Star, 1946-1977 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Clippings re: Washington Post, 1975-1977 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Color Schedules, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Comics Survey, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Complaint Letters - Philip W. Jackson Jr., 1975-1978 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Composing Room Instructions, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Composing Room Notes - Alexander Gordon, 1893-1939 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Content Report, January-February 1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Content Report, March-April 1976 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Content Report, May-June 1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Content Report, July-December 1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Copyright, 1953-1966 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Copyright Forms, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Credit Department, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Credit Policy, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Delinquent Accounts, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Department Heads Memos, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Editorial and News Coverage, 1919-1967 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Editorial and News Coverage, 1919-1967 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Editorial and News Coverage, 1919-1967 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Editorial and News Coverage - Negro in Washington, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Editorial Training Program, Undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Eight Paper Group, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Eight Paper Group, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Employee Training Manuals, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Employee Training Manuals, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Federal City Council, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Federal City Council, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Federal City Council, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Federal City Council, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Filing Procedures, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Garage, 1967-1976 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Graphic Arts Research Center - Rochester Institute of Technology, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Joan M. Heavey, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Hendrix Machine, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Historic Issues and Correspondence, 1876-1961 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Housing Data Reports v. Evening Star News, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Human Resources Form, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Indexing Manual, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - International Tennis Tournament, 1972-1975 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Invitations, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Invitations, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Job Ticket, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Kaufman and Associates Inc. - Marketing and Advertising Plans, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Kaufman and Associates Inc. - Marketing Report, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Knothole Club, 1962-1963 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Lawsuit - Free Standing Stuffer Inc., 1969-1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Legal Services - Seyfarth, Shaw, Fairweather and Geraldson, 1977-1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Library Orders, 1966-1975 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Library Orders, 1966-1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Library Orders, 1966-1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Library Survey, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Mail Center, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Make-up, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Make-up and Design, 1973-1977 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Management Training Exercises, Undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Map to Star Building, Undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Maps - Reference Materials, 1956-1961 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Maps: Their Care, 1956-1959 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Marketing - News From Time, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Marketing Research, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Marketing Research, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Maryland-Delaware-DC Press Association Inc., 1978 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Martin Marietta Corp. v. Evening Star Newspaper Co., 1977 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Martin Marietta Corp. v. Evening Star Newspaper Co., 1977 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - McCann-Erickson Inc. - Marketing Report, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Mechanical Developments, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Microfilming, 1954-1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Microfilming, 1954-1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Microfilming, 1954-1975 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Microfilming, 1954-1975 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Microfilming - Cartoons, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Microfilming - Clipping Files, 1970-1973 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Microfilming - Clipping Files, 1970-1973 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Microfilming - Clipping Files, 1970-1973 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Microfilming - Disposition Forms, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Microfilming - Index, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Microfilming - Invoices, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Microfilming - Invoices, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Microfilming - Invoices, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Microfilming - Invoices, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Microfilming - Invoices, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Microfilming - Invoices, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Microfilming - Invoices, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Don Miller, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Movies, 1951-1954 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Most Valuable Staffer Award, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Music Appreciation, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - National Symphony Orchestra Run, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - New Employee Information, 1947-1965 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Printing History, 1950-1952 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Noon Edition Proposal, 1934 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Office Supplies, 1975-1978 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Office Supplies, 1975-1978 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Oratorical Contest, 1924-1934 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Oratorical Contest - Clippings, 1924-1934 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Oratorical Contest - Publications, 1925-1930 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Order Forms, 1971-1976 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Paper Troopers, 1946-1949 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Parking Tickets, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Payroll, 1909-1976 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Payroll, 1909-1976 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Payroll, 1909-1976 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Payroll, 1909-1976 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Payroll, 1909-1976 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Payroll - Newspaper Guild Adjustments, 1930s (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Personnel Records, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Personnel Records, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Photography Department, 1964-1966 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Pictorial Magazine, 1954-1960 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Sylvia Porter - Your Money's Worth, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Postal Regulations, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Postal Service Rates, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Presentation: The Washington Star: A New Approach to Journalism, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1977-1981 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1977-1981 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1977-1981 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases/Addresses, Undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Press Reports, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Price and Wage Standards, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Printers' Publications, 1909 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Printing Plates - 50th Anniversary Edition, 1902 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Printing Plates - 100th Anniversary Edition, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Printing Plates - Incorporation, Undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Printing Plates - Title, 1902 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Printing Plates - Title, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Printing Press - Goss Co., 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Printing Press - History by Colonel Fred Cooke, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Printing Press - Memos, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Printing Press - Premier and Potter Printing Press Co., 1924 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Printing Press - R. Hoe and Co., Undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Printing Press - R. Hoe and Co., Undated (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Printing Press - R. Hoe and Co., Undated (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Printing Press - R. Hoe and Co., Undated (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Printing Press - Walter Scott and Co., 1934 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Production - Mechanical Time Schedules, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Production - Memorandum, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Promotions, 1966-1968 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Promotions, 1966-1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Promotions - Clippings, 1938-1967 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Promotions - Clippings, 1938-1967 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Promotions - Famous Presidential Campaigns, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Promotions - Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Promotions - Kemper Open (Photograph), 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Promotions - Kemper Open (Photograph), 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Promotions - Kemper Open (Photograph), 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Promotions and Public Relations - Budget, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Promotions and Public Relations - Budget, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Promotions - Super Star Maps, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Public Relations - Cocktail Party, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Purchase Orders - Subscriptions, 1956-1975 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Radio and Television - Clippings, 1938-1971 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Radio and Television - Clippings, 1938-1971 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - The Rambler - Index, Undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Rate Study, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate, 1954-1957 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate and Demographic Presentations, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Receipts, 1855-1898 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Redskins Album, 1967-1973 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Redskins Album - Cassette, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Redskins Album - Press Guide, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Relief Map Indexes, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Reprints, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Reprints, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Reprints - Mortgages, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Request for Reprint, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Rules, Undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Scali, McCabe, Sloves, Inc. - Marketing Report, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Scripps-Howard Newspapers, 1973-1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Send a Kid to Camp, 1976-1978 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Snapshot Contest, 1957-1969 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Snapshot Contest, 1957-1969 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Snapshot Contest, 1957-1969 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Snapshot Contest, 1957-1969 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Snapshot Contest, 1957-1969 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Space Allotments, 1962-1972 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Space Allotments, 1962-1972 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Special Interest Sections, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Special Sections, 1935-1963 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Speeches, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Sports Department - Clippings, 1950-1953 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Staff Savings Fund - Closing, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Star Building Floor Plans, Undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Star Games, 1947-1962 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Star Purchase - Stockholders, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Star Stock Purchase Agreement, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Star Trophy/Cup, 1938-1964 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Star Trophy/Cup, 1938-1964 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, 1952-1953 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Stockholder Reports and Financial Statements, 1952-1954 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Stock Purchase, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Style Book, 1903-1965 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Style Book, 1965-1966 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Style Book, 1965-1966 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Subject File Indexes, 1963-1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Subscription Advertisements, 1979-1981 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Subscription Rates, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Suburban Newspapers of America, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Supply Orders, 1970-1976 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Surveys, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Surveys, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Surveys, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Surveys - Reader Panel, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Sweepstakes, 1975-1978 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Syndicate Purchase, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Television Listings, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Third Street Ramp Problems - Southeast Freeway, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Time Inc. - Staff Directory, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Time Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Time Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Time Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Time Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Time Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Time Inc. - Presentations, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Time Inc. - Purchase of Star - Clippings, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Time Inc. - Purchase, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Trademark Registration, 1934 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Training Programs, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Travel Contest, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Unions, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Union Contracts - Boston, 1975-1977 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Union Contracts - Boston, 1975-1977 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Union Contracts - Boston, 1975-1977 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Union Contracts - Boston, 1975-1977 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Union - Newsclippings, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Union Newsletters, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Uptown Offices, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - VDT Training Manual, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Vending Machines and Newspaper Racks, 1935-1938 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Mark Vittert - Sale of the Star, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Washington Area Convention and Visitors Association, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Washington Diplomats Soccer Clinic (photographs), 1980 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Washington Diplomats Soccer Clinic (photographs), 1980 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Washington Diplomats Soccer Clinic (photographs), 1980 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Washington Publishers Association, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Washington Star Communications Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Washington Star Communications Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Washington Star Syndicate Inc., 1978 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Writing Contest, 1952-1962 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Yankelovich, Skelly, and White, Inc., 1978 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Youngs, Walker and Co., 1978 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Expansion, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Series 6: Clipping Files
  This series is made up of clippings, arranged alphabetically by subject, used as reference files by the staff at the Star.
  - Washing ton Star—News Coverage, Undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Washington Star—News—Editorials, Undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Washington Star—News—Endorsements, Undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Evening Star—News Coverage, Undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Evening Star, Undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Washington Star—News—Features, Undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Washington Star—Editors, Undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Star—Employees, Undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Washington Star—News—Daily News Purchase and Name Change, Undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Washington Star—News—History, Undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Washington Star—News—Time Magazine Purchase of, Undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Washington Star—News—Executives, Undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Washington Star—News—Carriers, Undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Washington Star—Labor, Undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Washington Star—Writer-In-Residence—Jimmy Breslin, Undated (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Washington Star—News—Employees, Undated (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Washington Star—News—Golden Gloves Tournament, Undated (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Washington Star—News—International Tennis Championship, Undated (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Washington Star—News—Sportsweek, Undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Washington Star—News—Sports—Pole, Undated (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Washington Star—News—Safety, Undated (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Washington Star—Comics, Undated (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Washington Star—News—Contests—Pro Picks, Undated (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Washington Star—Snapshot Contest, Undated (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Washington Star—News—Contests—Cashword, Undated (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Washington Star—News—Contests—Photo, Undated (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Star—Photo Contest, Undated (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Washington Star—News—Contests—Pruzzle, Undated (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Washington Star—News—Contests—Sweepstakes, Undated (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Washington Star—Contests (General), Undated (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Washington Star—Editions, Undated (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Washington Star—News—Editorial Dept., Undated (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Washington Star—News—Composing Dept., Undated (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Washington Star—Legal Action, Undated (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Washington Star—Photography, Undated (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Washington Star Communications Inc., Undated (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Washington Star—News—Vehicles, Undated (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Washington Star—News—Trucks, Undated (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Washington Star—News—Suits, Undated (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Washington Star—News—Star-Grams, Undated (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Washington Star—News—Rewards Offered, Undated (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Washington Star—Post Office Statements, Undated (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Washington Star—News—Survey, Undated (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - Washington Star—News—Circulation, Undated (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Washington Star—News—Circulation Dept., Undated (Box 61, Folder 45)
  - Washington Star—News—Advertising (4), Undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Washington Star—News—Advertising Dept., Undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Washington Star—News—Art Show, Undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Washington Star—News—Booklets, Undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Washington Star—News—Buildings—New, Undated (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Washington Star—News—Buildings—Old, Undated (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Washington Star—News—Business Dept., Undated (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Washington Star—News—Campaigns, Undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Star—News Camps, Undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Washington Star—News—Bloopers, Undated (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Washington Star—News—Awards—Research Grants, Undated (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Washington Star—News—Awards—Given, Undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Star—Awards—Given, Undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Star—Awards—Staff Members (2), Undated (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Star—The Evening, Undated (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Star—Awards—Received, Undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Washington Star—News—Awards—Received, Undated (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Washington Star (7), Undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Series 7: Labor, 1890-1980
  This series is made up of contracts, information on strikes, employee awards, and employee benefits. The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Awards - Maryland-Delaware-DC Press Association, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Pay, 1911 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Clippings - Employees, 1953-1967 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Clippings - Employees, 1953-1967 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Contracts - Typographical Union Scale, 1902-1907 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Contracts - Washington Newspaper Guild, 1940-1971 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Contracts - Washington Newspaper Guild, 1940-1971 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Employee Benefits, 1924-1943 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Glee Club, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Management Memo - Goodwin, 1890s (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Newspaperboys - Wages, 1970-1971 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Newspaperboys - Workmen's Compensation, 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Rules for Employees, 1903 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Salaries, 1935 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Staff Awards, 1949-1963 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Staff Awards, 1949-1963 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Star Club, 1925-1927 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Star Club, 1925-1927 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Star Club, 1925-1927 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Strikes - Clippings, 1951-1977 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Strikes - Clippings, 1951-1977 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Strikes - Clippings, 1951-1977 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Strikes - Clippings, 1951-1977 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Strikes - Clippings, 1951-1977 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Strikes - Clippings, 1951-1977 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Strikes - Correspondence and Contracts, 1974-1977 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Strikes - Machinists, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Unions, 1970-1976 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Series 8: Leadership, 1853-1979
  This series is made up of correspondence and financial records of both the owners of and the editors of the Star. Included in this series are the records of the Kauffmanns, the Noyes, Jim Daly, and Joseph Allbritton. Also included are records of the Estate of Jessie C. Kauffmann. The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Joe L. Allbritton - Resignation, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Jim Bellows, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - James J. Daly, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - James J. Daly, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - James J. Daly, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - James J. Daly - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - James J. Daly - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - James J. Daly - Expenses, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - James J. Daly - Letters of Congratulations, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - James J. Daly - Letters of Congratulations, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - James J. Daly - Rotary Club, 1975-1979 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - James J. Daly - Rotary Club, 1975-1979 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - James J. Daly - Telephone Log, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Editorial Staff, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Editors and Officers, 1963-1975 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Godwin, Undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - William H. Hope, Undated (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - John H. Kauffmann, 1935-1978 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - John H. Kauffmann, 1935-1978 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - John H. Kauffmann - Awards and Speeches, 1957-1970 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - John H. Kauffmann - Publicity, 1962-1970 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Phillip C. Kauffmann, Undated (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - R. M. Kauffmann, 1934 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Rudolph Kauffmann, 1927-1939 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Samuel H. Kauffmann, Undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Samuel H. Kauffmann - Congratulatory Notes re: Presidency, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Victor Kauffmann, 1910 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Herbert F. Korn, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Gidean A. Lyon, 1910-1951 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Ray F. Mack, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Robert L. Nelson, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Crosby S. Noyes - Correspondence, 1853-1940 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Crosby S. Noyes - Correspondence, 1853-1940 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Crosby S. Noyes - Correspondence, 1853-1940 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Crosby S. Noyes - Correspondence, 1853-1940 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Frank B. Noyes, 1925-1940 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Newbold Noyes, 1930-1942 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Theodore W. Noyes, 1922-1942 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Theodore W. Noyes, 1922-1942 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Theodore W. Noyes - 80th Birthday, 1938 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Theodore W. Noyes - 80th Birthday, 1938 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Theodore W. Noyes - Biographical, 1922-1939 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Theodore W. Noyes - Biographical, 1922-1939 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Theodore W. Noyes - Biographical, 1922-1939 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Theodore W. Noyes - Biographical, 1922-1939 (Box 67, Folder 8)